<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyAppWithAdMob</string>
    <string name="title_1">Mosque in Iran</string>
    <string name="description_1">this mosque is situated in iran. Iran is also a muslim country</string>
    <string name="title_2">Grand-Mosque-Sheikh-Zayed-Mosque-Abu-Dhabi</string>
    <string name="description_2">Grand-Mosque-Sheikh-Zayed-Mosque-Abu-Dhabi
    Its situated in UAE</string>
    <string name="title_3">faisal-mosque-islamabad</string>
    <string name="description_3">faisal-mosque-islamabad.Its situated in Pakistan</string>
    <string name="title_4">Aqs_,mosque_yaroshalam_phalasteen</string>
    <string name="description_4">Aqs_,mosque_yaroshalam_phalasteen. Its situated in Phalasteen (Israeel)</string>
    <string name="title_5">shahi_mosque_lahore</string>
    <string name="description_5">shahi_mosque_lahore. Its is situated in lahore pakistan</string>
    <string name="title_6">Masjid-e-Nabwi</string>
    <string name="description_6">Masjid-e-Nabwi. The Roza e Rasool Sallalaho Alaihi Wasalam. Its situated in Yasrub KSA</string>
    <string name="title_7">alharam_mosque_riaz</string>
    <string name="description_7">alharam_mosque_riaz. Its Qibal e Sani. Its is situated in Riaz Jiddah KSA</string>
    <string name="title_8">mosque_in_russia</string>
    <string name="description_8">mosque_in_russia. This mosque is situated in federation of russia old soviet union</string>
    <string name="title_9">aya_sofia_turkey</string>
    <string name="description_9">aya_sofia_turkey. previously it was known as a temple but later in 2020 MR. Presedent Erdugon converted it into a mosque. </string>
    <string name="title_10">sultan-omar-ali-saifuddien-mosque</string>
    <string name="description_10">sultan-omar-ali-saifuddien-mosque. I don\'t have much information about this mosque.</string>
    <string name="title_11">Siddiqa_Fatima_Zahra_Mosque_Kuwait</string>
    <string name="description_11">Siddiqa_Fatima_Zahra_Mosque_Kuwait. I don\'t have much information about this mosque.</string>


    <string name="Biography">Hi, every body \n This is Hafiz Muhammad Hasnain.\n
    I,m a bachelor of computer science. I have been as a android developer since May 2022.\n
        Working as a android developer its a great passion.\n If your are new to android then must start with kotlin.\n
        Its very power full advanced and comprehensive programming lanuage.\n
        Google have announced as a official language for writing all applications
        <h1>History of Kotlin</h1>\n
        Kotlin was developed by JetBrains in 2010.
        \n They initially released it under the name Project Kotlin in July 2011.\n
        They needed a language that was concise, elegant, expressive, \n
        and also interoperable with Java, as most of their products \n
        were developed in Java, including the Intellij Idea. They were looking \n
        for an alternate language to reduce the amount of boilerplate \n
        code required and to introduce new constructs, such as higher-order \n
        functions, to make language more expressive and concise.\n
        One of the goals of the Kotlin language was to \n
        be able to compile code as quickly as Java.
        \n So if you want to grow in as a android developer we must recommend you to start \n working with kotlin. Because its a new emerging \n technology having
        tremendous scope. So be quick and go to start.
    </string>
    <string name="Title0">Hafiz M Hasnain</string>
</resources>